http://www.oxfamireland.org/privacy

Skip to main content
Oxfam Ireland
Oxfam is a world-wide development organisation that mobilises the power of people against poverty
Change your consent | Revoke your consent
Privacy PolicyOxfam Ireland promises to take great care with your personal data, and we commit to protecting any personal information we obtain about you, whether you are a financial supporter, shopper, volunteer, employee/applicant or campaigner.Our Privacy Policy sets out how and why we obtain, use and protect personal information if you interact with us in one of the above roles. It is important that you read this Privacy Policy together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data.  See our Full Privacy Policy HereCookiesWe use “cookies” to identify you when you visit our website.What are cookies?Cookies are small text files that are transferred from the website to your computer, phone or tablet. Websites store cookies on your internet browser when you visit. Every time you return to the site and navigate around it picks up these bits of information. See our Full Cookies Notice HereContact usIf you would like more information, update your details or have any questions about these policies, please contact us by email at IRL-DataProtectionOfficer@oxfam.orgwrite to us at:Data Protection Officer Oxfam IrelandPortview HouseThorncastle StreetRingsendFREEPOST F927Dublin 4OrData Protection OfficeOxfam Ireland, Elizabeth House, Suite 1, 116 – 118 Holywood Road, Belfast, BT4 1NY, Northern Ireland Or call us on+353 (0) 1 672 7662 (ROI) or +44 (0) 28 9023 0220 (NI)
Join us
Sign up for updates and we'll let you know what Oxfam's up to, and how you can get involved.
* Email
Leave this field blank
CAPTCHACAPTCHAPlease tick the box below so we know your are a real person and not an automated spam submission.
Sign up!
Oxfam Ireland is a registered charity in Ireland (no. 2000946) and Northern Ireland (no. CHYXN 89651)
Oxfam Ireland is a member of the international confederation Oxfam.
Supported by
